trafficswarmresearch.com 2010-06-08

# Traffic Swarm Research

###  Privacy Policy

**1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from me?**

Traffic Swarm Research collects information in several ways from different parts of our website. Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, Traffic Swarm Research requires a unique email address and private password. We may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests so we may target the surveys you receive and contact preferences. Wherever Traffic Swarm Research collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

**2\. What are cookies and how are they used by** **Traffic Swarm Research?**

Traffic Swarm Research may place Internet cookies on your hard drive. Internet cookies are small files that may be placed on your hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies are used to (a) remind us of who you are in order to deliver you better service; (b) estimate our audience size by determining repeat usage of the Web site to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior; (c) track your progress in surveys; and (d) measure certain traffic patterns for use as a research tool to understand how our users' habits are similar or different from one another. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. By not accepting cookies, some Web pages may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information.

Traffic Swarm Research also collects IP addresses (the Internet address of a computer) to track a user's session while the user remains anonymous. We analyze this data for certain trends in statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there. In those limited cases where session information is not anonymous, Traffic Swarm Research will provide notice of the practice and an opportunity to “opt out”.

Research companies that you may take surveys with through Traffic Swarm Research may also use their own cookies. The content of such cookies and the use of the information they contain is controlled by the individual research companies, not by Traffic Swarm Research.

**3\. How is my information used?**

Traffic Swarm Research will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information to others without your consent. The information you provide will be used to support your relationship with Traffic Swarm Research. Your information may be shared with agents, contractors, or business partners for the purpose of performing services for Traffic Swarm Research.

We want to help you quickly find information on Traffic Swarm Research and alert you to specific surveys, updated information, and other new opportunities from Traffic Swarm Research. Accordingly, we may send you direct mailings, or contact you by telephone about our various surveys and other opportunities we feel may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply “opt-out” by the means provided for in the mailings or by clicking Contact Us.

Traffic Swarm Research does research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us during your use of the Traffic Swarm Research Web site. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. Traffic Swarm Research may share this aggregated data with others.

**4\. Who is collecting my information?**

When you are on the Traffic Swarm Research site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Traffic Swarm Research alone, unless specifically stated otherwise. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than Traffic Swarm Research, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not participating in that particular survey.

Please also be aware that Traffic Swarm Research research partners that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those Web sites linked to Traffic Swarm Research either through advertisements or other hyperlinks are not covered by this privacy statement.

**5\. With whom does** **Traffic Swarm Research share my information?**

Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide with other Traffic Swarm Research agents, contractors or our business partners for the purposes of performing services for Traffic Swarm Research. Traffic Swarm Research may share aggregated data with others. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information.

Traffic Swarm Research may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Traffic Swarm Research’ Terms of Use or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Traffic Swarm Research' rights or property, other Traffic Swarm Research users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Traffic Swarm Research may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

**6\. How do I access, update or delete my information?**

You can request the individual information that Traffic Swarm Research has collected about you, correct factual inaccuracies in your information, remove personal information from Traffic Swarm Research’ data bases, and/or update your personal information by clicking Contact Us or updating your information on our website.

**7\. What does “opt-out” mean?**

To “opt-out” means that you have notified Traffic Swarm Research that we no longer have permission to use your information for a particular purpose. For example, when we send you information on a new survey, you will be given the opportunity to "opt-out" of receiving such information in the future.

**8\. What else should I know about my privacy?**

Third party Internet sites and services accessible through Traffic Swarm Research have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Traffic Swarm Research has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please be careful and responsible online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your information, Traffic Swarm Research cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information through the transmission process and you do so at your own risk. 

**9\. What about my children and their use of your Web site?**

Our Website is currently available only to persons Thirteen years of age or older. We do not collect user information from any visitors indicating they are under thirteen years of age.

**10\. How can this policy be changed?**

If we wish to change this policy, we will publish the changes on this website at least 30 days before those changes take effect. We will also notify registered users of changes to this policy by electronic mail. As always, if you do not agree with any changes to our privacy policy, you have the option of requesting that we delete your personally identifiable information from the site.

**11\. Additional Questions**

Questions regarding this privacy statement should be directed to Cleave Voice Surveys using Contact Us.
